Bojan Čoka

software developer

coka@fastmail.com · https://github.com/

Experience

DevTech (Apr 2016-)

Junior Software Developer

Description: At DevTech, I have been working on systems that support cloud infrastructure providers. Currently, I am working as a remote team member for a fintech startup based in London. I am also helping shape DevTech's R&D and internal education efforts. **Skills:** C#, F#, Microsoft SQL Server, Entity Framework, TypeScript, React, Redux.

Rendered Text (Jul 2015-Oct 2015)

Intern Software Developer

Description: Rendered Text is a software company making SemaphoreCI, a hosted continuous integration and deployment service. I worked on the user-facing part of Semaphore (a Ruby on Rails web application). At Rendered Text, I learned about the principles of object-oriented programming, behavior-driven development, and software design. I had the privilege of working alongside colleagues with various backgrounds, such as marketing, which helped me learn how to communicate technical ideas effectively in order to create the most value for Semaphore's users. **Skills:** Ruby on Rails, CoffeeScript, AngularJS, Vagrant.

3Lateral (Aug 2012-Sep 2012)

Intern Technical Artist

Description: 3 lateral is a digital character workshop responsible for some of the best facial rigs in the video game industry. During my time there, I was tasked with creating an animation-ready character face from scanned data. This gave me the opportunity to experience a production environment first-hand. **Skills:** Autodesk Maya (and its Python API), Pixologic ZBrush, facial anatomy, FACS.

Education

Faculty of Technical Sciences (2011-present)

Bachelor of Computer Graphics 8.22/10.00

Jovan Jovanović Zmaj Grammar School (2007-2011)

Natural Sciences 4.64/5.00, with honors (physics)

Certificate of Proficiency in English (2010)

79/100 (Grade B)

Other

Resonate (Apr 2014-)

Festival Attendee

Description: Over the years, I have attended several workshops at the Resonate festival in Belgrade. In 2015, I earned a scholarship for an advanced workshop of choice. These workshops were themed around interactive real-time graphics. We used various creative coding frameworks and programming languages to achieve an aesthetic result, often on constrained platforms, such as the Raspberry Pi, or in Internet browsers. **Skills:** WebGL, three.js, OpenGL (core profile), OpenGL ES, openFrameworks.

Summary

My primary area of expertise is computer graphics, and creative coding is my primary passion. I have a solid understanding of the graphics pipeline at the low level (transformations, illumination models, and GPU acceleration). I am working on marrying this understanding with strong software engineering practices in order to create meaningful computer programs.